# **Daisuke Nagata**

Full Stack Blockchain Engineer

## Profile

I am a passionate and creative software engineer who has been working on myskills since high school with 10 years of experience. I have been educated and trained in modern IT techniques. I worked with a myriad of web and mobile technologies, frameworks, practiced both building apps from scratch and contributing to large pre-existing projects with legacy code. Over the last 4 years, mainly focusing on blockchain technology such as Solidity | Web3 | Ether | Polka | Solana | Solana-Web3. Really, eager to participate any DEFI & DApp firms and boost the project with my enthusiasm & experience. Throughout my career, I have completed many web app projects across different verticals, ranging from large companies to startups. I always keep up with the latest news and developments in the web and blockchain world through meetups and self-teaching.

## Employment History

## Full Stack Blockchain Developer at QUBE, United States

Feb 2021 — Nov 2021

- Developed a multichain platform that combines the most popular functions of the crypt world
- Developed Ethereum smart contract with solidity and frontend with React and web3, ether.js

#### Solana | React Developer at Synergy Land, United States

Oct 2020 — May 2021

- Developed a ARPG game to earn NFTs while playing powered by Solana
- Developed Solana-web3 with React based frontend
- Developed Solana-Rust for contract deployed to testnet and devnet

## FE & web3 Developer at OpenDao, United States

Dec 2019 — Oct 2020

- Developed an over-collateralized & multi-collateral stable coin to make abridge between DeFi and real world assets
- Improved loading performance of the application by 30% through implementing cache storage and optimization technologies with Next and Redux
- Collaborate with UI/UX designers to build a responsive experience with React and TainwindCSS to ensure consistent delivery of a high-quality dynamic UI and intuitive UX for the user per the design specifications

## Lead Developer at FudFarm, United Kingdom

Nov 2018 — October 2019

- Developed an crop farming app that allows users to stake his farm land to start earning the crop token
- Developed Ethereum smart contract with solidity and frontend with React and web3, ether.js
- Connect wallets(metamask, walletconnect) to the app

#### Location

Osaka, Japan

#### Contact

daisukenagata0209@gmail.co m

**Telegram** 

Skype

#### Links

GitHub

Website

#### Skills

JavaScript

TypeScript

Python

Solidity

C

C#

Golang

Rust

Web3.js

React.js

Node.js

Next.js

Gatsby

Vue

Vuex

Angular

Docker

Git

GraphQL

## Blockchain Developer at PepeDapp, United States

Feb 2018 — Nov 2018

- Developed and deployed smart contract on Etheruem blockchain for a meme marketplace and wallet for digital art collectors and artists
- Developed frontend by React and web3

## Full Stack Developer at SEO Genie, Israel

Sep 2016 — Dec 2017

- Gained hands-on expertise in React, Redux, Bootstrap, GraphQL, Node.js, MongoDB, Docker
- Various React Native & Ionic application development
- Conducted unit and load testing for high-profile customer-facing applications, which reduced system failure rate by 70%
- Experienced all project phases using Agile & DevOps methodologies
- Experienced crypto wallet and blockchain technology
- Worked with a highly trained team automated by DevOps and CI/CD

## Lead Developer at Allgive, United States

Aug 2015 — Jul 2016

- Built an unique micro-donation system using React, Node.js, AWS
- Worked with a team of 3 junior FE developers

## Web Developer at Hiprez Team, United States

Feb 2014 — Jun 2015

- Improved legacy web by replacing it with React and Rest API, Laravel. Resulted into 50% faster loading times
- Worked with a team of 10+ developers and QA, scrum masters

## Education

## Software Engineering, Osaka University, Osaka, Japan

2009 — 2013

#### **Relevant Coursework:**

Information technology, Application Development, Bioinfomatics and Biocomputing, Computer Graphics and Interaction, Computer Networks, Computer Vision, Cyberphysical Systems, Cybersecurity, Embedded Systems, High Perfomance Computing, Information System and Databases, Intelligent Devices, Intelligent Systems, Machine Learning, Mathmatical Methods, Software Engineering, Software Verification and Testing, Sound, Speech and Natural Language Processing

HTML5 & CSS3
Bootstrap
TailwindCSS
MongoDB
Express.js
РНР
Laravel
Symfony
Django
Kubernates
Jenkins
Languages
English